<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<contentList>
	<content contentuid="he6eb02f6g1539g4c48g9dedg7f053bedaa16" version="1">Psion</content>
	<content contentuid="h44603d09g9250g4d6bg8a7egd981cca2caf8" version="1">Psions learn to manipulate the world with the wondrous power of their minds. Drawing upon the mystical power within, they can communicate without speaking, move objects, alter their physical bodies, and even manifest spells.</content>
	<content contentuid="h5af6d8f1g5778g4f5fgb20bga1575563ab36" version="1">Psi Points</content>
	<content contentuid="hb9807d77g87c5g4511ga3dcg59e911baedf1" version="1">Psi Points are spent to cast spells, equal to the spell's level.</content>
	<content contentuid="h04c9011cgc5e6g41fcgaa0fg0a941bfe895e" version="1">Mental Limit</content>
	<content contentuid="h13cf3603g28b7g474ag8895g67274f66b919" version="1">Determines the highest level spell you can cast using your Psi Points.</content>
	<content contentuid="h465c7c80g8c66g4489gb557g936b84841143" version="1">Psionic Magic</content>
	<content contentuid="h6ea4dde0g063bg4dd6g9b02gc1b1202624e3" version="1">You can cast spells using Psi points.</content>

	<content contentuid="hf5c35c61g8923g4b5eg9602g9ab55547f461" version="1">Celerity I</content>
	<content contentuid="hf34c447egacddg4070gb8cag25e99274c653" version="1">Your walking speed increases by 3 meters, and you can take the Dash action as a bonus action on your turn.</content>
	<content contentuid="h2baed13ag0e32g4c76g8653gc01679bbb27c" version="1">Celerity II</content>
	<content contentuid="hf206caa7g6b17g480cga8fbg137457ec4dee" version="1">Prerequisite: 5th level Psion, Celerity I - Your walking speed increases by another 5 feet, and when you Dash, opportunity attacks against you have disadvantage.</content>
	<content contentuid="h61ff6853gdf77g4ff3g88a4gb94e95901c9c" version="1">Celerity III</content>
	<content contentuid="hdc5b73a0gc0a6g4f27gba65g96c28a85e908" version="1">Prerequisite: 11th level Psion, Celerity I, II - Your walking speed increases by an additional 5 feet. Also, when you Dash, you ignore the effects of all difficult terrain, and you can move along vertical surfaces and across liquids without falling during your movement on that turn.</content>
	<content contentuid="ha602d29ag0a28g46acgbe39gd28bf5336af0" version="1">Celerity IV</content>
	<content contentuid="hda58dc03g9f45g434ega45fgba80e4f29995" version="1">Prerequisite: 16th level Psion, Celerity I, II, III - When you make a Dexterity saving throw to take only half damage from a spell or effect, you instead take no damage if you succeed on the save, and only half damage if you fail. Also, when you make a Dexterity check or saving throw, you can use your Intelligence score, in place of Dexterity.</content>
	<content contentuid="h6402c176g93a7g4a96gaa7cgf0ecfdb01116" version="1">Mystic Talents</content>
	<content contentuid="ha19a73c4g4b00g46fdg9a7bgadd98745bd85" version="1">Below are the Mystic Talents available to a Psion. If a Talent has a prerequisite, like your Psion level or another Talent, you can learn it at the same time you meet the prerequisites. If a Talent allows you to learn a cantrip, it doesn't count against your total number of Cantrips Known. If you already know that cantrip you learn a Psion cantrip of your choice.</content>
    
	<content contentuid="[]" version="1"></content>

    <content contentuid="h5134be88ge79bg40cbg9f1cg5e372694c110" version="1">Iron Durability I</content>
	<content contentuid="he83f5514g529ag422bg8813g7466af7f70c3" version="1">So long as you are not wearing armor or wielding a shield, your &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ArmourClass"&gt;Armour Class&lt;/LSTag&gt; is equal to 13 + your Intelligence modifier.</content>
    <content contentuid="hec6ea75ag1ac9g4ea9g9ea3g1970b2a04534" version="1">Iron Durability II</content>
	<content contentuid="h40706c6dgb694g4674g8f06gee13260aecfb" version="1">Prerequisite: 5th level Psion, Iron Durability I - As a bonus action, you can spend 1 Psi Point to grant yourself temporary hit points equal to your Intelligence modifier (minimum of 1 temporary hit point)</content>
    <content contentuid="ha7c8535bg0611g4bf6g8f19gbcdbb4333cc9" version="1">Iron Durability III</content>
	<content contentuid="h55fe786eg6ab6g43e4gab50gec2d9a0a6947" version="1">Prerequisite: 11th level Psion, Iron Durability II - Whenever you take damage, you can use your reaction to expend 3 Psi Points and gain resistance to the triggering damage type until the start of your next turn.</content>
	<content contentuid="h1a40d3e6gd2bag442fgbdc8g3c97b3ff14f9" version="1">Iron Durability III: Defense</content>
	<content contentuid="h01b5f695gf96cg46ddg84c4g3046c51ffea8" version="1">Whenever you take damage, you can use your reaction to expend 3 Psi Points and gain resistance to the triggering damage type until the start of your next turn.</content>
    <content contentuid="h802b53aegd3e8g4488gbe68g8773279fc8f5" version="1">Iron Durability IV</content>
	<content contentuid="h53062f72g5f24g466dg82efgfe5e22f65fb7" version="1">prerequisite: 16th level Psion, Iron Durability III - Whenever you make a saving throw you gain a bonus to your roll equal to your Intelligence modifier (minimum of +1).</content>

    <content contentuid="h362c8446ga2c9g4edaga7c1g9ed1a9f61f96" version="1">Precognition I</content>
    <!-- <content contentuid="h13a9ac81g7748g43c5gb92bgf2d0b9fd117f" version="1">Precognition I</content> -->
    <content contentuid="h270111f5g8da5g41e6gbec0g053a2eb9ca80" version="1">Precognition II</content>
    <content contentuid="hf3913ec0g1c33g4ce4ga71fg6a70f9e89b6f" version="1">Prerequisite: 5th level Psion, Precognition I - As a reaction when you are hit by an attack, add [1] to your &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ArmourClass"&gt;Armour Class&lt;/LSTag&gt; against the triggering attack, potentially turning a hit into a miss.</content>
    <content contentuid="ha46c69a1g1c80g46a8g9b8bg2222ad4de804" version="1">Precognition II: Psionic Parry</content>
	<content contentuid="h42882c04g28e5g400cga51egfe4ca2f8468c" version="1">As a reaction when you are hit by an attack, add [1] to your &lt;LSTag Tooltip="ArmourClass"&gt;Armour Class&lt;/LSTag&gt; against the triggering attack, potentially turning a hit into a miss.</content>
    <content contentuid="hd0997bd1g200bg4c49gabafg705323b6977f" version="1">Precognition III</content>
    <content contentuid="h9c1547c3g1c4fg420eg9e53g7b5b5f77baa5" version="1">Prerequisite: 11th level Psion, Precognition II - As a bonus action on your turn, you can spend 3 Psi Points to enter a heightened precognitive state for 1 minute. While in this state, attacks targeting you cannot be made with advantage, and critical hits become normal hits. You must concentrate on this ability as if concentrating on a spell.</content>
    <content contentuid="hda7d43fbg19f1g4427g9185g6c7450208263" version="1">Precognition III: Heightened Awareness</content>
	<content contentuid="h7387ae92g91dfg4347ga6b7gded81bd89b69" version="1">As a bonus action on your turn, you can spend 3 Psi Points to enter a heightened precognitive state for 1 minute. While in this state, attacks targeting you cannot be made with advantage, and critical hits become normal hits. You must concentrate on this ability as if concentrating on a spell.</content>
    <content contentuid="h8924b897g17f9g45bagb2e7ga3f7c8f2b4c8" version="1">Precognition IV: Quick Reflexes</content>
	<content contentuid="hf293672eg6c49g43c2g89bfg7595798fe048" version="1">prerequisite: 16th level Psion, Precognition III - When you roll initiative you can take an extra action on your first turn. Also, while you are in your heightened precognitive state, all attacks targeting you are made with disadvantage.</content>

    <content contentuid="he3a8a39ag2aebg44c1ga0b1g9da7525d32ed" version="1">Metamorphosis I</content>
	<content contentuid="he2b8c29fg5dd8g4ac8g9b3fgeff8fd7eb307" version="1">You learn psionic strike, making your unarmed damage equal to [1] + [2] and when you make an unarmed strike, you use your Intelligence modifier, in place of Strength or Dexterity, for the attack and damage rolls.</content>
    <content contentuid="h2da896a0gaef7g4b40g90abg145a303bb8c6" version="1">Metamorphosis II</content>
	<content contentuid="h3f31d6d1g6784g4e36gb9ceg8c397599a32b" version="1">Prerequisite: 5th level Psion, Metamorphosis I - As a bonus action you can expend 1 Psi Point to transform, becoming Large or Tiny, gaining the respective benefits: \nLarge. You gain temporary hit points equal to your Psion level + your Intelligence modifier, your reach increases by 5 feet, and your melee attacks deal 1d4 extra damage on hit. \nTiny. You have advantage on Dexterity (Stealth) checks and you can fit through 6-inch gaps without having to squeeze.</content>
    <content contentuid="h3cca98a2g1da4g44a5g8aa7g7b4b609d372a" version="1">Metamorphosis III</content>
	<content contentuid="h19231a46gafd2g447cg8837gea0da680bac2" version="1">Prerequisite: 11th level Psion, Metamorphosis II - As a bonus action you can spend 3 Psi Points to transform as if you had cast polymorph on yourself. While transformed in this way you retain your mental ability scores and personality.</content>
    <content contentuid="h200861d6gb9b3g452bga601g85e3f6c20bca" version="1">Metamorphosis IV</content>
	<content contentuid="he696ea1eg5955g4b1dga1feg4a4b4508ede1" version="1">Prerequisite: 16th level Psion, Metamorphosis III - As a bonus action you can expend 5 Psi Points to transform,becoming Huge or Diminutive, gaining the following benefits:Huge. You gain temporary hit points equal to twice yourPsion level + your Intelligence modifier, your reach increasesby 10 feet, and your melee attacks deal 2d6 extra damage.Diminutive. You gain a +10 bonus to Dexterity (Stealth) checks, attacks made against you have disadvantage, and youcan fit through 1-inch gaps without squeezing. While you are Diminutive, you are too small to make weapon attacks.</content>

    <content contentuid="[HANDLETalent_RestorationIName]" version="1">Restoration I</content>
	<content contentuid="[HANDLETalent_RestorationIDesc]" version="1">You learn the spare the dying cantrip. It doesn't count against your total number of Cantrips Known. When you manifest spare the dying, it has a range of 30 feet.</content>
	<content contentuid="[HANDLETalent_RestorationIIName]" version="1">Restoration II</content>
	<content contentuid="[HANDLETalent_RestorationIIDesc]" version="1">Prerequisite: 5th level Psion, Restoration I - You have a pool of healing power that can restore [1] hit points. As an action, you can touch a creature and draw power from the pool to restore a number of hit points up to the maximum amount remaining in your pool. You can't heal undead or constructs. Your healing pool replenishes when you finish a long rest.</content>
	<content contentuid="[HANDLETalent_RestorationIIIName]" version="1">Restoration III</content>
	<content contentuid="[HANDLETalent_RestorationIIIDesc]" version="1">Prerequisite: 11th level Psion, Restoration II - As an action, you can touch a willing creature and expend 2 Psi Points to end one of the following conditions affecting it: blinded, charmed, deafened, frightened, poisoned, or stunned.</content>
	<content contentuid="hf9113b18g9530g4c8aga544g0f5113031402" version="1">Cure a creature from blinded, charmed, deafened, frightened, poisoned, or stunned.</content>
	<content contentuid="[HANDLETalent_RestorationIVName]" version="1">Restoration IV</content>
	<content contentuid="[HANDLETalent_RestorationIVDesc]" version="1"></content>
</contentList>