<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<contentList>
	<content contentuid="he6eb02f6g1539g4c48g9dedg7f053bedaa16" version="1">Psion</content>
	<content contentuid="h44603d09g9250g4d6bg8a7egd981cca2caf8" version="1">Whether through years of practice, or a once in a generation innate talent, Psions learn to manipulate the world with the wondrous power of their minds. Drawing upon the mystical power within, they can communicate without speaking, move objects, alter their physical bodies, and even manifest spells. Relying solely on mastery of their mind, Psions can perform feats thought impossible, even by the most erudite Wizards and devout Clerics. For Psions, it is a point of great pride that they can produce wonders without the help of external power. Due to their potential, Psions are often misunderstood and feared by the common folk. If they don’t learn to control their power, their strange abilities can cause them to be shunned and hated by those around them. Most Psions reveal their power only when necessary, and are hesitant to trust others.</content>
	<content contentuid="h5af6d8f1g5778g4f5fgb20bga1575563ab36" version="1">Psi Points</content>
	<content contentuid="hb9807d77g87c5g4511ga3dcg59e911baedf1" version="1">Psi Points are spent to cast spells, equal to the spell's level.</content>
	<content contentuid="h04c9011cgc5e6g41fcgaa0fg0a941bfe895e" version="1">Mental Limit</content>
	<content contentuid="h13cf3603g28b7g474ag8895g67274f66b919" version="1">Determines the highest level spell you can cast using your Psi Points.</content>
	<content contentuid="h465c7c80g8c66g4489gb557g936b84841143" version="1">Psionic Magic</content>
	<content contentuid="h6ea4dde0g063bg4dd6g9b02gc1b1202624e3" version="1">You can cast spells using Psi points.</content>
	<content contentuid="hf5c35c61g8923g4b5eg9602g9ab55547f461" version="1">Celerity I</content>
	<content contentuid="hf34c447egacddg4070gb8cag25e99274c653" version="1">Your walking speed increases by 3 meters, and you can take the Dash action as a bonus action on your turn.</content>
	<content contentuid="h2baed13ag0e32g4c76g8653gc01679bbb27c" version="1">Celerity II</content>
	<content contentuid="hf206caa7g6b17g480cga8fbg137457ec4dee" version="1">Prerequisite: 5th level Psion, Celerity I - Your walking speed increases by another 5 feet, and when you Dash, opportunity attacks against you have disadvantage.</content>
	<content contentuid="h61ff6853gdf77g4ff3g88a4gb94e95901c9c" version="1">Celerity III</content>
	<content contentuid="hdc5b73a0gc0a6g4f27gba65g96c28a85e908" version="1">Prerequisite: 11th level Psion, Celerity I, II - Your walking speed increases by an additional 5 feet. Also, when you Dash, you ignore the effects of all difficult terrain, and you can move along vertical surfaces and across liquids without falling during your movement on that turn.</content>
	<content contentuid="ha602d29ag0a28g46acgbe39gd28bf5336af0" version="1">Celerity IV</content>
	<content contentuid="hda58dc03g9f45g434ega45fgba80e4f29995" version="1">Prerequisite: 16th level Psion, Celerity I, II, III - When you make a Dexterity saving throw to take only half damage from a spell or effect, you instead take no damage if you succeed on the save, and only half damage if you fail. Also, when you make a Dexterity check or saving throw, you can use your Intelligence score, in place of Dexterity.</content>
	<content contentuid="h6402c176g93a7g4a96gaa7cgf0ecfdb01116" version="1">Mystic Talents</content>
	<content contentuid="ha19a73c4g4b00g46fdg9a7bgadd98745bd85" version="1">Below are the Mystic Talents available to a Psion. If a Talent has a prerequisite, like your Psion level or another Talent, you can learn it at the same time you meet the prerequisites. If a Talent allows you to learn a cantrip, it doesn't count against your total number of Cantrips Known. If you already know that cantrip you learn a Psion cantrip of your choice.</content>
</contentList>